Architecture Slide Collection
Yale University Arts Library
- 20th Century Architecture (Box 41)
  - United States (Box 61)
    - Miscellaneous Cities [Slide box 377] (Box 63)
      - San Francisco, CA [Slide box 480] (Box 80)
        - Houses (Box 80)
          - Various (Box 80)
          - Kahn House (Box 80)
          - Russell House (Box 80)
        - Housing [Slide boxes 480-481] (Box 80–81)
        - Museums [Slide box 481] (Box 81)
        - Office Buildings (Box 81)
        - Stores (Box 81)
      - San Jacinto, CA (Box 81)
      - San Jose, CA (Box 81)
      - San Juan Bautista, CA (Box 81)
      - San Juan Capistrano, CA (Box 81)
      - San Luis Rey de Francia, CA (Box 81)
      - San Mateo, CA (Box 81)
      - San Miguel, CA (Box 81)
      - San Pedro, CA (Box 81)
      - San Rafael, CA [Slide box 482] (Box 81)
      - San Simeon, CA (Box 81)
      - Santa Barbara, CA (Box 81)
        - Various (Box 81)
        - Houses (Box 81)
          - Slavin House (Box 81)
          - Tremaine House (Box 81)
        - Schools (Box 81)
      - Santa Fe, NM (Box 81)
      - Santa Monica, CA (Box 81)
        - Various (Box 81)
        - Eames House (Box 81)
        - Gehry House (Box 81)
      - Santo Domingo, NM (Box 81)
      - Sarasota, FL (Box 81)
        - Various (Box 81)
        - Clubs (Box 81)
        - Houses [Slide box 483] (Box 81)
          - Umbrella House (Box 81)
          - Kate Wheelan House (Box 81)
        - Schools (Box 81)
          - High School Riverview (Box 81)
          - High School II (Box 81)
      - Saratoga Springs, NY (Box 81)
      - Saugus, MA (Box 81)
      - Sausalito, CA (Box 81)
      - Savannah, GA (Box 81)
      - Saybrook, CT [Slide box 484] (Box 81)
      - Scarsdale, NY (Box 81)
      - Schenectady, NY (Box 81)
      - Scottsdale, AZ (Box 81)
      - Seal Harbor, ME (Box 81)
      - Sea Ranch, CA (Box 81)
        - Condominium (Box 81)
      - Seaside, FL (Box 81)
      - Seattle, WA (Box 81)
      - Sedona, AZ (Box 81)
      - Shaftsbury, VT (Box 81)
      - Sharon, CT (Box 81)
      - Sharon Springs, NY [Slide box 485] (Box 81)
      - Shelburne, VT (Box 81)
      - Short Hills, NJ (Box 81)
      - Shreveport, LA (Box 81)
      - Sidney, OH (Box 81)
      - Slatersville, RI (Box 81)
      - Smithfield, VA (Box 81)
      - Soames Sound, ME (Box 81)
      - Solvang, CA (Box 81)
      - Southampton, NY (Box 81)
      - South Bend, IN (Box 81)
      - Southbury, CT (Box 81)
      - South Carolina, State of (Box 81)
        - Berkeley Co. (Box 81)
        - Charleston, Co. (Box 81)
      - South Coventry, CT (Box 81)
      - South Norwalk, CT (Box 81)
      - Southport, CT (Box 81)
      - South Windsor, CT (Box 81)
      - Springfield, IL (Box 81)
      - Springfield, MA (Box 81)
      - Spring Green, WI (Box 81)
        - Hillside Home School [Slide box 486] (Box 81)
        - Taliesin East (Box 81)
          - Exterior (Box 81)
          - Interior (Box 81)
      - Stamford, CT (Box 81)
      - Stanford, CA (Box 81)
      - State College, PA (Box 81)
      - Staten Island, NY (Box 81)
      - Stockbridge, MA (Box 81)
      - Stonington, CT (Box 81)
      - Stony Creek, CT (Box 81)
      - Sturbridge, MA (Box 81)
      - Suffield, CT (Box 81)
      - Sunland, CA (Box 81)
      - Sunnyvale, CA (Box 81)
      - Swampscott, MA [Slide box 487] (Box 82)
      - Syracuse, NY (Box 82)
      - Tacoma, WA (Box 82)
      - Tallmadge, OH (Box 82)
      - Tampa, FL (Box 82)
      - Tarrytown, NY (Box 82)
      - Tenafly, NJ (Box 82)
      - Tennent, NJ (Box 82)
      - Thousand Oaks, CA (Box 82)
      - Topeka, KS (Box 82)
      - Topsfield, MA (Box 82)
      - Torresdale, PA (Box 82)
      - Trampas, NM (Box 82)
      - Trento, NJ (Box 82)
      - Truro, MA (Box 82)
      - Tucson, AZ (Box 82)
      - Tulsa, OK [Slide box 488] (Box 82)
      - Tuxedo Park, NY (Box 82)
      - Two Rivers, WI (Box 82)
      - Tyrone, NM (Box 82)
      - Utica, NY (Box 82)
        - Various (Box 82)
        - Fountain Elms (Box 82)
        - Munson William Proctor Museum (Box 82)
      - Vail, CO (Box 82)
      - Valley Forge, PA (Box 82)
      - Valyermo, CA (Box 82)
      - Vancouver, WA (Box 82)
      - Vergennes, VT (Box 82)
      - Venice, CA (Box 82)
      - Venice, FL [Slide boxes 488-489] (Box 82)
      - Ventura, CA [Slide box 489] (Box 82)
      - Vina, CA (Box 82)
      - Virginia, State of (Box 82)
        - Various (Box 82)
        - Bedford Co. (Box 82)
          - Poplar Forest (Box 82)
        - Charles City Co. (Box 82)
          - Berkeley (Box 82)
          - Shirley (Box 82)
          - Westover (Box 82)
        - Fairfax Co. (Box 82)
          - Various (Box 82)
          - Gunston Hall (Box 82)
          - Mt. Vernon (Box 82)
        - Fluvanna Co. (Box 82)
        - James City Co. (Box 82)
          - Carter's Grove [Slide boxes 489-490] (Box 82)
        - King George Co. [Slide box 490] (Box 82)
        - Lancaster Co. (Box 82)
        - Prince George Co. (Box 82)
        - Surrey Co. (Box 82)
        - Westmoreland Co. (Box 82)
          - Stratford Hall (Box 82)
      - Virginia Beach, VA (Box 82)
      - Virginia City, NV (Box 82)
      - Vista, CA (Box 82)
      - Waltham, MA (Box 82)
        - Various (Box 82)
        - Christopher Gore House (Box 82)
        - Brandeis University (Box 82)
      - Warren Township, NJ [Slide boxes 490-491] (Box 82)
      - Washington, CT [Slide boxes 491] (Box 82)
      - Washington, D.C. (Box 82)
        - Various (Box 82)
        - Views (Box 82)
        - Plans/Planning (Box 82)
        - Airports (Box 82)
        - Churches (Box 82)
        - Clubs [Slide box 492] (Box 82)
        - Government Buildings (Box 82)
          - Various (Box 82)
          - Central Heating Plant (Box 82)
          - Capitol (Box 82)
          - Federal Reserve Building (Box 82)
          - Pan American Building (Box 82)
          - State Department Building (Box 82)
          - White House [Slide box 493] (Box 83)
        - Hotels (Box 83)
        - Houses (Box 83)
        - Housing (Box 83)
        - Libraries (Box 83)
        - Monuments (Box 83)
        - Jefferson Memorial (Box 83)
          - Lincoln Memorial (Box 83)
          - Vietnam Memorial (Box 83)
          - Washington Monument [Slide box 494] (Box 83)
            - Various (Box 83)
            - Competition Entries (Box 83)
        - Mosques (Box 83)
        - Museums (Box 83)
          - Various (Box 83)
          - National Gallery of Art (Box 83)
            - Various (Box 83)
            - East Building (Box 83)
          - Smithsonian Museum (Box 83)
        - Stations (Box 83)
      - Waterbury, CT (Box 83)
      - Waterford, PA (Box 83)
      - Watertown, WI (Box 83)
      - Waterville, ME (Box 83)
      - Waukegan, IL (Box 83)
      - Wayland, MA (Box 83)
      - Wayzata, MN (Box 83)
        - Various (Box 83)
        - Dayton House [Slide box 495] (Box 83)
      - Wellesley, MA (Box 83)
      - Wellfleet, MA (Box 83)
      - Wernersville, PA (Box 83)
      - West Bend, IA (Box 83)
      - West Columbian, TX (Box 83)
      - West Coxsacki, NY (Box 83)
      - Westerly, RI (Box 83)
      - West Medford, MA (Box 83)
      - WestPoint, NY (Box 83)
      - Westport, CT (Box 83)
      - West Warwick, RI [Slide box 496] (Box 83)
      - Westwood, CA (Box 83)
      - Wethersfield, CT (Box 83)
        - Various (Box 83)
        - Houses (Box 83)
          - Various (Box 83)
          - Peter Burnham House (Box 83)
          - Buttolph-Williams House (Box 83)
          - Buttolph-Williams House (Box 83)
      - Wheeling, WV (Box 83)
      - Whitemarsh, PA (Box 83)
      - Wickford, RI (Box 83)
      - Williamsburg, VA (Box 83)
        - Various (Box 83)
        - Governor's Palace [Slide boxes 496-497] (Box 83)
        - Houses [Slide box 497] (Box 83)
        - Schools (Box 83)
          - Various (Box 83)
          - William and Mary (Box 83)
      - Williamstown, MA (Box 83)
      - Willow Run, MI (Box 83)
      - Wilmington, DE (Box 83)
      - Winnetka, IL (Box 83)
      - Winnfield, LA (Box 83)
      - Winona, MN (Box 83)
      - Winslow, AZ (Box 83)
      - Wiscasset, ME (Box 83)
      - Wisconsin, State of (Box 83)
      - Woburn, MA [Slide boxes 497-498] (Box 83)
      - Woodbridge, CT [Slide box 498] (Box 83)
      - Wood's Hole, MA (Box 83)
      - Woodside, CA (Box 83)
      - Woodstock, NY (Box 83)
      - Woodstock, VT (Box 83)
      - Woonsocket, RI (Box 83)
      - Worcester, MA (Box 83)
      - Wyntoon, OR (Box 83)
      - Yellow Springs, OH (Box 83)
      - Yemassee, SC (Box 83)
      - Yonkers, NY (Box 83)
      - York, ME (Box 83)
      - Yorktown, VA (Box 83)
      - Yorktown Heights, NY (Box 83)
      - Ypsilanti, MI (Box 83)